JUAN FONSECA

iffonseca24@gmail.com | Venezuela, Guayana | +58 4120854351 | lilfon.github.io/Portfolio

SUMMARY

I am a developer with experience in web applications, algorithms, and data structures. I consider myself a responsible, dedicated and constant person, learning every day to be a better version of myself. In the lasts years i've training in the frontend ambit.

SKILLS

Frontend Development, React.js, Next.js, CSS, HTML, Styled Components, Third Party Code Interpretation, Javascript, Angular.js, Jest, SQL, Node.js, Express, Postman, Typescript, Git.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Bachelor Degree | Catholic Andrés Bello University (2022).

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer, Intership | Lcc Opentech (03/2021 - 05/2021)

 A virtual store was developed with a client-server architecture using Next.Js, React.Js, Adobe XD, WordPress, Git and CMS tools and technologies.

Backend Developer, Apprenticeship | University Project (09/2019 - 01/2020)

 An Android mobile application for the management of the university semester was developed for civil, industrial and computer engineering students, working with the Dart programming language.

Fullstack Developer, Apprenticeship | University Project (02/2019 – 07/2019)

 A management web platform was developed for a pet store franchise, using an MVC architecture pattern, an SQL Database was modeled according to the proposed business and Laravel, PostgreSQL, PHP and JavaScript technologies were used.

COURSES

- React.js Advanced | Platzi platform.
- Node.js Fundamentals | Platzi platform.
- JavaScript Professional | Platzi platform.
- React Router & Redux | Platzi platform.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Linkedin profile, https://www.linkedin.com/in/juanfranciscofonseca/
- All approved courses (57 in total), https://platzi.com/p/JuanFonseca/